♪ My royal day
can be a royal bore ♪
♪ it leaves me colder
than a basement floor ♪
♪ the only moment
I keep waiting for ♪
♪ is when the day
will be through ♪
♪ I never notice
if it's dark or clear ♪
♪ what people say to me
I hardly hear ♪
♪ the passing hours
are an endless year ♪
♪ until at last
I'm alone with you ♪
♪ every night at 7:00 ♪
♪ you walk in
as fresh as clover ♪
♪ and I begin to sigh
all over again ♪
♪ every night at 7:00 ♪
♪ you come by
like may returning ♪
♪ and me, oh, my,
I start in yearning again ♪
♪ you seem to bring ♪
♪ faraway spring ♪
♪ near me ♪
♪ I'm always
in full bloom... ♪
♪ When you're
in the room ♪
♪ for every night
at 7:00 ♪
♪ every time
the same thing happens ♪
♪ I fall once again
in love ♪
♪ but only with you ♪
♪ Every night at 7:00 ♪
♪ every time
the same thing happens ♪
♪ I fall once again
in love ♪
♪ but only with you ♪
May I say your performance
was a bit ragged?
You were so slow going around the
throne, I almost caught you.
Well, the audience seemed to like it.
Whew! It's so hot in New York
in the summertime.
I'm glad we're closing
tomorrow night.
Wonder what happened
to the air conditioning.
Mr. Hiller probably turned
it off to save money.
Oh, would you blot my face, too?
Up here.
It's trickling.
And who's Mr. Hiller?
The house manager.
You ought to know that.
You've been playing his theater
for the past year and a half.
Oh, is that that evil little man
who comes around and pinches?
That's your department, sister dear.
All I can say is let Mr. Hiller
keep his air conditioning.
He can't take it with him,
and where he's going, he'll need it.
Oh, boy, it's hot.
Say, if ever I play a king again,
I'm going to be one
of those Asiatic boys
who just wears earrings and a sheet.
Hey, what's your hurry?
Pete.
Hi, Ellen honey.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
You know my brother Tom, don't you?
No, I don't believe
I've had the pleasure.
How are you?
I'm fine, sir,
and thank you for asking.
I'll be out in 5.
Oh, my, Pete, you look
so nice and cool.
Make yourself at home, won't you?
Sit down anywhere.
Oh, how was it, sir?
Hot.
Oh, your agent stopped
by to see you, sir.
Irving? What brought him out
this clammy night?
He didn't say. He just told me
to tell you it was imperative
that you and miss Ellen
meet him at McGuffy's bar
next door right after
the performance.
Oh. Ellen.
Yeah.
Irving wants us to meet him
at McGuffy's.
OK. How'd you like Pete?
Isn't he cute? He's from the south.
No.
Why, Ellen honey,
I never would've guessed it.
He owns miles and miles
of tobacco land in Virginia,
and you ought to hear him chant.
I met him 2 days ago
at Hilda swan's house,
and I'm simply mad about him.
Is that all?
That's all.
Roger.
Miss Ellen seems quite
taken, doesn't she?
This will probably be one of those long
affairs that drags on a whole weekend.
The big news overseas
concerns the royal wedding in London.
The British capital is
already festive and happy
in anticipation of the wedding,
which is still several weeks off.
Towel.
As for the Princess,
the most closely guarded secret since radar
is her wedding gown.
The Princess herself
will see it for the
first time this weekend.
Please, Mr. Bowen.
Chester, I...
in other news, in Miami, Florida,
a new tropical hurricane
seems to be approaching...
can I talk now?
Yes, sir.
You know, Mr. Bowen,
I danced in Trafalgar square
the day her grandfather was married.
I'd give anything to be
there again this fall,
wouldn't you?
Yes. I like weddings,
provided, of course,
they're not mine.
Oh, marriages are very healthy, sir.
They say married men live
much longer than bachelors.
If that's true, they're only
trying to outlive their wives
so they can be bachelors again.
Haven't you ever thought
of getting married, sir?
Once, as a matter of fact, I did.
The young lady changed her
mind at the last moment.
I've been deeply indebted
to her ever since.
Good night, Chester.
Gee, I wonder what Irving wants.
I hope it's something that...
my gosh, what a muscle.
It's like cement.
Oh, it's nothing.
All us tobacco men get kind of strong.
What from?
Lifting money.
Come now, it wasn't that good.
Good night, Eddie.
Good night.
He's the only stage door man
I know who isn't called pop.
Hello, will.
Gee, it's been a long time.
Hi, Irv.
Oh, I couldn't wait for you
back stage tonight.
What is with that heat over there?
Who needs it? So how was the show?
Well, the first act was a little...
doll boat, how are you, baby?
Fine. How are you?
You look so sweet tonight.
Ooh, I do, don't I?
OK, come on, order.
I got news, big news.
Oh, Irving, can I present Pete Cumberly?
Let's have it.
Well, how do you do, Mr. Cumberly?
It's a great pleasure.
Thank you, sir.
That's very nice.
Who is this square?
Friend.
Tom Collins, please.
Nothing for me, thank you.
Hit me with a rot.
Shall I give it to you?
Well, come on.
What is it?
This'll kill you. My brother
Edgar called tonight from England.
He's the head of our London office.
Been there for years.
The Mayfair theater people want
your whole show for London.
No.
But quick. They want you there
during the wedding season.
England during the wedding.
I like that.
Oh, Tommy.
Ellen honey, does this mean
you'll be leaving me?
Oh, yes, Pete. Isn't it wonderful?
When do we open?
As soon as possible. Of course,
you got to rehearse the English cast first.
Hit me, son.
What about transportation?
There's some French boat
leaving a week from next Monday.
Which one?
Who knows what the name?
It's in French.
Don't worry.
I'll get you on it.
Ellen, this means we'll be
saying good-bye in 10 days.
Oh, yes, Pete, and I'm so happy.
Ellen.
Oh, hello, Dick.
I was waiting for you back stage.
That's why I'm late.
Ellen, who is this fella?
Finish your drink, Pete.
Did you hear the good news?
We're going to England,
and we're going to be there during the wedding.
What are you doing here, sir?
What do you mean?
Who's he?
A friend.
What are you doing here, sir?
I demand an answer.
Go peddle your papers,
will you? When do you leave?
That's an insult.
What's an insult?
What's the matter with you?
This is terribly embarrassing.
I forgot all about Dick.
Hope they don't hurt each other.
I think we ought to start packing.
I have to buy all my new
clothes before I go over.
You'll have time.
I'll send the rest of the company
over the week after you leave.
I wonder what they'll be wearing.
I don't know. Pay the man,
will you, Irving?
Yeah, sure.
How much do we owe you?
May I?
Yes, you may.
And keep the change.
I have a little business to take care of.
I'll meet you on deck.
OK, sister dear.
Hello, Billy.
This is good-bye.
Thanks for coming down to see me off.
It's hard saying good-bye like this
after all we've been to each other.
Oh, I know. It's been a lovely 3
days, but I'll be back soon.
Oh, dear, I must go now.
May I walk you up the gangplank?
I'd rather you wouldn't.
You understand?
No.
Well, it's just better that way.
Write to me, Billy.
I will.
Good-bye, Ellen.
I'll miss you very much, Linda.
I can tell you that knowing
you these past few weeks
has been one of the most exciting
things that's ever happened to me.
To me, too, John.
Pete!
Ellen honey,
I thought I went to the wrong deck.
You haven't much time.
Really? And I had
so much to say.
What?
Well, you're gonna be away...
yes, I know, Pete, but what?
And suddenly knowing
you're gonna be away
makes me realize my feelings for you,
so I thought I'd...
I mean... Ellen honey...
visitors ashore, please.
You'll have to go now.
Good-bye.
But, Ellen honey...
you better hurry. Write me
what you had to say, huh?
I will.
Bye.
I can tell you, Barbara,
that knowing you these past few weeks
has been one of the most exciting
things that's ever happened to me.
Oh, I'll miss you, John.
Good-bye, baby.
Good-bye, Irv.
I know you'll be a smash.
Now, if you want anything,
you ask my brother Edgar.
He's gonna meet you at the hotel.
So long, Irv.
Bye.
So, listen, have a good time.
So long, Ellen.
So long.
Bye, honey. Bye.
See you soon.
So long.
See you.
Hey, who you waving at up there?
That girl right there, see?
That's my girl.
Don't give me that.
I'm betting 8 to 5 on Dixie boy.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. This is...
fellas, now look...
Poor Irv.
Hold it. Now listen...
What a beautiful, beautiful day.
Isn't it wonderful?
We don't know a soul on the boat,
and we can have fun
together for a change.
Yeah.
Good day.
Oh, well, I don't know him, Tom.
Honest, I don't.
I want to write a letter.
OK, baby. Don't forget,
we've got to rehearse.
What time shall I meet you?
2:00 sharp in the gym.
I won't keep you long.
I'll be there.
Don't worry.
Now don't be late.
OK.
Good day.
There's carbon paper
in the middle drawer
if you want to make duplicates.
I'm not writing a letter.
I was just doodling,
waiting for an opportunity
to introduce myself.
Uh, my name is Brindale,
Lord John Brindale.
And what's yours?
Bowen, duchess Agatha Bowen.
Oh, no, no.
Really, what is it?
Let's see, now.
"E.B."
"E."
is that Ethel?
Wait a minute.
Bowen. Why, of course.
You're Ellen Bowen, aren't you?
You're doing fine.
It's very stupid of me.
I should've known.
Why, I only saw your
show a few weeks ago.
Please forgive me.
Oh, that's all right.
I know you have a lot on your mind.
Oh, I can explain
those 2 little episodes
that you witnessed yesterday.
Oh, you can?
Yes.
Then go ahead.
Go ahead.
Well, you see...
They're both terribly nice girls,
and they're both so fond of me
that I... well,
I couldn't bear
depriving either one of them.
You know how it is.
In order to be kind to people,
one has to be a very, very good liar.
T-tell me, why were you following me?
Following you?
I was doing no such thing.
I was only saying good-bye
to a couple of...
the same?
Yes.
Does this sort of thing
happen to you very often?
All the time. And you?
Constantly.
I guess we're both 2 kind people.
Yeah.
I have to get a stamp.
Do you live in New York?
No. I've been there on
business for some time,
but I'm just going home
now for the wedding.
The royal wedding?
Yes.
You're going to the wedding?
I'm escorting someone, yes.
You really are a lord, aren't you?
I'm afraid so.
My, my.
Haven't you ever met anyone
who held a title before?
Only Joe Louis.
Do you know I'm very glad
that you're Ellen Bowen?
Why?
Because that means
that chap you're with
is your brother and not your husband.
Do you know what I did last night?
No. What?
I surveyed this whole boat,
and I discovered
that you were the most
attractive girl on board.
Well, thank you.
And I kept thinking that "what
a pity it is she's married,
because that's going to make
things terribly awkward."
But it isn't going to be
awkward at all now.
Thanks for the use
of the hall, purser.
Not at all.
If you see my sister on deck,
will you tell her I'm waiting for
her, please?
I will.
I like your boat.
Thank you, monsieur.
Oh, monsieur Bowen,
I have a favor to ask.
On every crossing, you know,
we have a gala benefit for disabled seamen,
and I was wondering if you and
your sister would dance for us
on that night.
Oh, we'd love to.
Just tell us when.
Just one number would be sufficient.
We don't want to ask...
no trouble at all.
I know it's an imposition to ask you
two, but I would feel...
we'd love to. Don't worry.
We'll do it.
There's a fella that won't
take yes for an answer.
Oh, fine. Thanks for
showing up at rehearsals.
Oh. Oh, John, this is my brother Tom.
Tom, this is John.
How do you do?
Glad to know you.
I just picked up John
in the writing room.
So I gathered.
He's a real lord.
Oh, it's nothing at all.
Miss Bowen.
Yes?
Cable.
Oh, thank you.
Excuse me, please.
Oh, Tom... Tom,
it's from Pete.
Says he's very blue,
except for his eye, which is black.
Uh, let's forget Pete
for this trip, shall we?
Excuse us.
Looks a little grim out there.
Yeah.
It does.
Monsieur Bowen,
I'm wondering if you and your sister
will dance right away instead
of waiting until 10:30.
We're a little afraid of the weather.
You mean, it might be
a little... Rocky?
Yes.
That won't bother us.
We can handle it.
Thank you, monsieur.
Any time you say.
I better change my dress.
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ there's a sapphire sky
above us ♪
♪ high above us ♪
♪ made for you ♪
♪ when you open your eyes ♪
♪ open your eyes ♪
♪ there's a carpet
of Jade around us ♪
♪ laid around us ♪
♪ all for you ♪
♪ when you open your eyes ♪
♪ let me
show you the sights ♪
♪ take you ♪
♪ on a tour
of this great, new ♪
♪ fabulous world
we own ♪
♪ we alone ♪
♪ so open your eyes ♪
♪ and you'll see
how this momentary ♪
♪ ordinary ♪
♪ night can seem ♪
♪ more unreal than a dream ♪
We can handle it, all right.
What do we do now?
Keep your balance.
Oh, sure.
So sorry.
Pardon us.
What?
Isn't it wonderful, Tommy?
It sure is.
Hello? Yes? Oh, sure.
Yes. Do come on up.
Room 211, 12, and 14.
OK.
Who was that?
Edgar Klinger, Irving's brother.
He's coming up.
I'm so happy, Tommy.
I wonder what the Princess
is doing this morning.
Why don't you call her and ask her?
Wonder what I'd be doing
a month before my wedding.
Probably trying to figure
a way to get out of it.
Do you really think so?
You know you would, and so would I.
How do you do?
I'm Edgar Klinger.
We didn't know...
That Irving and I were twins?
No, we didn't.
Oh, I must say,
he should have told you, you know.
After all, this is a pretty box of pickles.
May I come in?
Well, of course.
I'm sorry.
How do you do?
So happy to meet you at long last.
My, it's amazing.
Yes, it is rather, isn't it?
I do hope the rooms are satisfactory.
Oh, they're fine.
It's a miracle you could get them.
Yes, quite. The wedding
has packed things up a bit,
but, uh, then there are ways.
How's everything in the theater?
Oh, seems to be humming.
The dancers are coming to audition this
afternoon, the singers tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Oh, hello, Johnny.
How are you?
Ellen's boat romance: John brindale.
Do you know him?
Know the family.
Very old.
They do say that young
John is a bit of a chaser.
Didn't have to chase very hard after Ellen.
She stood still and waited.
This afternoon?
No, they're auditioning all day.
Just a minute.
Tom, you don't need me this afternoon, do you?
John wants me to drive down
and see his old country home.
I suppose it's all right,
but I should think you'd want to come
along and see who you're working with.
Well, I never notice anyone but you.
John, I...
I want you home for dinner.
And no dates at night
until after we open.
You'll come strolling in
at 4:00 in the morning
and be all tired out next day.
Yes, papa. All set.
What time will you pick me up?
OK. I'll be ready.
Bye, John.
Shall we?
Yeah. See you at 7:00.
And be back.
Oh, I will.
I will.
Cheerio.
Good-bye, Edgar.
Oh, and if there's anything you
need, do call.
Thank you.
After you.
Tell me, old boy,
how are things in the colonies these days?
Oh, fine. Fine.
These English clothes are terrific.
Frightfully amusing tie, what?
Yeah.
Got a match?
Thanks. I hear that shaving
lotion's great stuff.
Did you ever use it?
Oh, every day.
Sorry. I thought
you were him.
How odd. Thank you.
Well, I must get back to the office.
You know where the theater
is, don't you? Sure.
Well, I'll see you later.
Cheerio. OK.
Hello again.
I wish you'd stop following me.
Following you?
I'm not a bit flattered.
Mr. Bowen. I'm Charles Gordon,
your stage manager.
Oh, it's nice to see you.
Everything's ready, sir.
Oh, good. See that girl in
the green dress near the end,
changing her shoes?
Yes, sir.
Let's begin with her.
They can each show me a few steps.
Very good, sir.
Your name, please?
Anne Ashmond.
Thank you. Will you begin, please?
Why, yes.
Miss Anne Ashmond.
Will you try a few steps
with me, please?
Oh, dear.
Can't you dance with a partner?
Well, I could till a moment ago.
Well, try.
We'll take something easy to start.
May I have a pickup, please?
You should've seen the expression
on your face when you saw me.
How did I look?
As if I were a dentist.
You dance very well.
Thank you.
I think you'll do fine.
Will I really?
Sure.
It's very nice of you not to
hold what happened against me.
I do a little bit.
Well, what can I do?
You can have dinner
with me some night.
Well, I should love to.
How about tonight?
Well, I don't know.
I, uh...
she'll do fine. Pick you up at 8:00.
Thank you. Who's next?
Is it much further?
No. We're almost there.
My, you look pretty.
I know. What do you
have to do at the house?
Get the wedding present.
We sold practically everything at auction,
except for one set of China plates.
I was supposed to get those
when I got married.
Seeing there's precious
little chance of that,
we decided to hand them on
to the prince and Princess.
Why is there precious little chance?
Oh, I don't know.
I think you have to enjoy
living with yourself
before you have nerve
to ask anyone else to.
Besides, you know how I am.
Oh, here we are.
John, it's beautiful.
Yes, it was.
I think they're in here.
Oh, what a wonderful
floor to dance on.
Yes.
How long since anyone's
lived here, John?
Oh, about 5 years.
No one can afford
places like this today.
I imagine you miss it terribly.
No, I don't think I do anymore.
I just don't have anything
to replace it with.
I say, what time
do you have to be back?
7:00 sharp.
Oh, I wish you could
have dinner with me.
I don't know when I'll
get another free evening.
There's some sort of party
every night from now on.
Can't you?
I don't know.
You know how Tom is.
Will you try?
Yes, I'll try.
Good.
Hello.
Hi. Back on time.
How was the afternoon?
Oh, it was wonderful.
How were your dancers?
Dancers.
What do you want to do tonight?
Oh, I'm kind of tired, Ellie.
I thought I'd just skip
dinner and go straight to bed.
Would you mind?
Oh, no, no.
It's a good idea.
That country air
really knocks me out.
Yeah.
Sure you don't mind?
Oh, gosh, no.
As a matter of fact,
I think I'll turn in right now,
if it's all right with you?
It's a good idea.
Yeah.
It's been a kind of a rough day.
Good night, honey.
Good night, Tommy.
Sweet dreams.
Taxi, please.
Thank you.
Taxi.
More coffee?
Thank you.
Yes, Ellie and I have done
quite a few shows together.
Do you like to dance?
Yes, yes.
It's hard work, but it's fun.
What made you decide to dance?
Oh, a very silly reason.
How silly?
Well, when I was 11,
I fell in love for the first time
with a boy much older.
12?
Mm-mmm. 13.
His name was Alonzo,
and I was so happy
that suddenly all I
wanted to do was to dance,
so I figured that if I
danced when I was happy,
I should be happy if I danced.
Is that silly enough?
I think so.
I felt so good about Alonzo
I used to close my eyes and pretend
I could dance all over the floor,
walls, even the ceiling.
If you ever learn to do that,
I can get you a very good booking.
You want anything else?
No.
Let's go.
You better not take me home.
Why not?
It's a long way, and
besides, this is Friday.
And Friday I have to stop
and see my father.
Oh, I'd like to meet him. Cabby!
All right. Uh, what's the address?
150 Mitchell street.
Cabby, could you take us
to 150 Mitchell street?
Love to, governor.
Love to.
Wait, will you please, driver?
Love to, governor, love to.
See? That's my father.
He's the proprietor.
Oh, dear. I do hope
he won't offend you.
He's quite impossible, really.
He and my mum have been
separated for 3 years,
and I have to stop here every
Friday and get her money.
Why doesn't your mother do it?
They're not speaking to each other.
So I says to him
"McBride, every time you get 4 drinks
"under that belt of yours,
"you become a bloomin' nuisance.
"And what's more,
every time you fall down,
you chip a piece out of
the bar with your chin."
So I says,
"from now on..."
Annie! Well, my little
girl, how are you, dear?
Hello, Jamie. Tom, this is my father.
Father, this is Tom Bowen.
Glad to know you,
Mr. Ashmond.
Pleased to meet you, sir.
To the royal couple.
Bowen, eh?
I used to know a Willy Bowen.
Good old Willy.
Married a girl
we used to know named Gladys Oxley.
I don't think you knew Gladys, Annie.
Very happy they were for years.
Then one night, good old Willy
threw her right out of the window.
Nobody knows why.
But I always figured that
they must've had an argument.
I don't suppose you'd
be any relation.
Why, no. I don't believe I
have any relatives over here.
Over here?
I'm from America.
America?! Get out of my pub!
Leave the premises!
I'm not on speaking terms
with the United States!
Jamie! How dare you bring
another yank to my tavern!
Out, do you hear?
Out!
Wait. What's the matter
with the United States?
Matter? You owe me
money, you do.
Where is it?
Here, look at this.
£2.10 run up by
your bloomin' soldiers,
and what do they do?
Upped it!
Walked out without payin'!
I'll not serve you a drink, sir.
Now stop it, Jamie.
To the royal couple.
Well, I can't allow
Anglo-American relations
to be threatened like this.
I'd like to square that bill.
Tom, you shouldn't.
Oh, sure. How much
is that? £2.10?
There you are, sir.
Now there's a gentleman for you.
Not at all like that other
yank you're so fond of.
Yes. Now,
you can just add 10 Bob to that
and give it to me for mother.
Has she found out when
we go to the palace yet?
Or is she keepin' it from me?
£3.00, Jamie.
You see, we sent a little token
to the royal highnesses
for the weddin',
and accordin' to the
papers, anybody who did
are allowed to see
the weddin' presents.
That's a nice custom.
£3.00, Jamie.
Oh, all right. Here.
What you countin' for?
Don't you trust me?
Just like her mother...
no faith.
You're 5 shillings short.
Oh? That's what you might
call a typographical error.
Here.
Thank you.
We'd better go.
Good night, Jamie.
Good night, dearie.
Good night, pal.
Good night, buddy.
To the royal couple.
Thanks.
Looks like mother is still up.
Ever since she and Jamie separated,
she can never get to
sleep till I get home.
Let's walk a minute
and get some nice fresh fog.
Who, uh...
who's the yank you're so fond of?
Hal Rayton.
He's my fiancé.
You don't sound very happy about it.
Oh, I am, really.
Is it a secret?
No. Well, this
is ridiculous.
He's in Chicago.
Illinois?
He lives there.
And you live here?
Yes.
If you keep that arrangement
after your marriage,
you'll be very happy.
How long since you've seen him?
Oh, about 2 years.
2 years?
And you're still in love with him?
Well, I've never
thought of not being.
Do you hear from him very often?
Every few days, as a rule.
Actually, I haven't heard
from him for 2 months now,
but he's probably been busy.
I wrote to him tonight
and told him I was in your show
and asked him to call
me opening night.
I assume you have some plans about
getting together in the future.
Oh, yes.
Are you going over there,
is he coming over here,
or are you going
to meet in the middle?
You see, he works in Ogilvy's
department store in Chicago.
Oh? Well?
As soon as he makes
enough to send for me...
Or I make enough to go over there,
we're going to be married.
That's fine.
You... you don't
mind, do you?
Mind what?
My getting married, I mean.
I should love to go
out with you again.
I had an awfully good time.
So did I. Of course, I don't mind.
Actually, I'm kind of glad
you're all tied up.
Now we can go out and have fun
without any pressure, can't we?
Yes...
I guess so.
Good night, Anne.
Good night, Tom.
Yes, this is New York.
We have him on the line.
Mr. Irving Klinger,
we're ready with Mr. Edgar
Klinger in London.
Go ahead, please.
Hello, ed?
This is Irv!
How are you, twinsey?
Buzzing, old boy.
Simply buzzing.
I got a fast note by air
mail from Tombo this morning.
He says everything is terrif.
Oh, well, that is good news.
Tell me, have you heard from Tom?
No. How are things?
Oh, absolutely superb.
I think we shall have
a fantastic opening
night tomorrow night.
What about Ellen?
Tom having trouble
keeping her caged up at night?
Oh, no. Quite
the contrary.
She's been frightfully conscientious.
Goes straight home from
the theater each night.
Tom's the one who's
been romping about.
Tom? No kidding?
What'd he do, catch himself a chick?
No, no, no.
Tom's quite well.
He's taken a fancy to
some girl in the show.
Pretty little thing she is, too.
Hey, Eddie, what
I called you about...
call me after the opening, will you?
That light in the window's
gonna be me sitting and waiting.
I will, old boy.
Don't give it a second thought.
Oh, by the by, how's the mater?
Oh, mom's fine.
Oh, splendid.
Do give her a peck on the cheek for me.
I got you.
Dig you tomorrow night.
Pip now.
"Pip now"?
"Dig you"?
What's all the commotion
about down there?
It's some regiment that hasn't
paraded its finery in years.
Gosh, you can just feel the
excitement growing, can't you?
After all, the wedding's
only a week off.
I wonder what the groom
is doing this morning.
Why don't you call him and ask him?
Very funny.
I thought it was.
What time did you get in last
night, lover boy?
Oh, around 11:00,
I guess.
I don't know.
I didn't pay much attention.
Well, I did.
It was around 2:00.
My, you're a busy little man these
P.M.S, aren't you?
We were just having a few laughs.
Just a few laughs.
That's all.
Come in.
Morning.
Why, Johnny,
what a pleasant surprise.
How are you?
Fine.
Hi, John.
Hello, Tom.
I thought this was as
good a place as any
to see the parade.
Oh, we have a sensational view.
Oh, before I forget...
your ticket for the opening.
Second row, right on the aisle.
Wonderful.
Thanks very much.
What time is the parade?
It should pass here any minute.
I say, Ellen,
wonderful seeing you again.
How's the show going?
Oh, just fine.
It's been a long time.
I know. 4 days.
Look, tomorrow night
after the opening,
Edgar's giving a party.
You're going with me, OK?
OK. It'll take a little
doing, though.
Why?
There's a huge affair being given,
and I'm supposed to take someone.
But you can get out of it, can't you?
This is my opening night.
Besides, if you don't
take me, nobody will.
I haven't been out with a
soul but you since I got here.
I'll get out of it.
You're looking so well these days.
Thank you.
I think about you so much.
I think about you, Ellen. What?
I said, I think about you.
It's so different from
anything I've ever felt before.
How?
Well, first of all,
I'm not interested
in anybody or anything I do,
and that's completely new for me.
I say, that's completely new for me.
Ellen, I think that this
is getting very serious.
What a parade.
I've never seen anything
like it in my life.
Parade?
Oh, is it over?
I'll tell them to come back.
Ignore him, Johnny.
I'm so excited about tomorrow night.
Come on, girl.
We're due at the
theater 5 minutes ago.
In a minute.
Do you realize we've only
been out at night together
about 3 times since I've been here?
Well... come on, come on.
Just a minute.
What's that you're playing, Tom?
The song she's supposed to be
rehearsing at the theater now.
Well, why don't you rehearse it here?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Is that all right with you, Tommy?
All right.
♪ I wake up and sigh
each morning ♪
♪ happy the night's
gone by ♪
♪ I wake up and pray
each morning ♪
♪ pray that the day
will fly ♪
♪ and then I
sit back and smile ♪
♪ and dream of that day ♪
♪ when I'll be standing
by your side, my love ♪
♪ the happiest day
of my life ♪
♪ how my heart will swell
with pride, my love ♪
♪ the happiest day
in a lifetime ♪
♪ then as the last words
are spoken ♪
♪ the bells in the steeple
will chime ♪
♪ and I will love you so ♪
♪ and you will see ♪
♪ it will be ♪
♪ for a lifetime ♪
Hold it. Hold it, please.
Charlie, what time is it?
Uh, it's 4 A.M., sir.
Well, that's enough.
All right, everybody.
That'll be all for tonight.
I'm sorry to keep you
working so late.
What about our last 2 numbers?
We don't have to rehearse those.
You were fine on them this afternoon.
Yeah, I thought so, too.
Show looks pretty good, doesn't it?
Not bad.
Anne?
Yes?
Excuse me.
Don't forget tomorrow night.
The opening?
How could I?
Oh, yes, do try to make that.
We'd love to have you.
No, I meant afterward.
Edgar's giving a party.
We'll go together.
Oh, Tom, I can't.
You can't?
Why not?
Hal is calling me.
That's right.
I forgot all about him.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I wouldn't bother,
except I haven't heard from
him in such a long time now,
and I do have to talk to him.
Taking the bus home tonight, Anne?
I'll be right with you.
I'm sorry, Tom.
That's all right.
It's all right.
What time tomorrow, sir?
3:00 for the company.
11:00 for miss Bowen and me.
Yes, sir.
11:00?
What for, Tom?
I wanna take those 2 numbers
we didn't do tonight.
I thought you were
satisfied with them.
There's still a few rough spots.
Say, what happened to you?
Did you get stood up?
What are you talking about?
My, what a manic-depressive
life you lead.
It's going to be a marvelous
party tomorrow night.
I'm going with John.
Who are you taking?
♪ Every night at 7:00 ♪
♪ dum bum bum Dee um... ♪
Where's the key?
You have it.
I have not.
I gave it to you.
I suppose I'll have to go all
the way down to the desk...
see? If you think
nice things,
all doors open to you.
Is that your message for the day?
Flowers! For me?
I wonder who they're from.
Not from me.
Well, that I know.
Who?
It's from John.
He can't make the opening.
He can't?
My, what a shame.
I had a feeling this morning he
wasn't gonna be able to make it,
but he just didn't
know how to tell me.
Now, isn't that terrible?
He's weak,
and I just hate weak people!
Yes, dear, I know you do.
Up one minute, down the next.
What a manic-depressive
life you lead.
Oh, all right, all right.
So we're even.
Who are you going
with tomorrow night?
I don't know.
Well, why don't you take me?
I think we should go together
anyway, don't you?
After all,
we're the stars of the show.
Yes, I think we should.
Miss Bowen, may I escort you
to Klinger's clambake tomorrow night?
Why, I'd be delighted!
And what a surprise you're askin' me!
Oh, Tommy,
let's be terrific tomorrow night.
We'll be cosmic.
Stupendous!
A smash! We hope.
And, Ellen, don't forget...
that's still the
most important thing.
Yes, Tommy...
I know it is.
Good night.
Oh, yeah, yeah!
You listen to me just once!
Oh, sure, sure!
I told you a million times.
You never wanna listen to me.
So I said it, so you heard
it, so you're mad.
So what?
So this...
it's the last time
I ever go to a party with you!
Will you put that in writin'?
You're always makin'
cracks, makin' cracks!
Like what?
You always humiliate me, humiliate me.
Didn't your mother never
teach ya no manners?
I ain't never had no mother.
We was too poor.
Say, what's the matter
with you lately?
You used to tell me you loved me.
You used to treat me
like a high-class dame.
Well, usen't ya?
So I used.
There. So you
admit it.
I ain't admittin' nothin'!
I'll give ya one more chance.
Do you love me or don't ya?
No, I don't!
Quit stallin'!
I want a direct answer.
Listen, kid, there's one thing
about you I can't understand...
♪ how could you
believe me ♪
♪ when I said
I loved you ♪
♪ when you know I've been
a liar all my life? ♪
♪ You've had that reputation
since you was a youth ♪
♪ you must've
been insane ♪
♪ to think I'd
tell you the truth ♪
♪ how could
I believe you ♪
♪ when you said
we'd marry? ♪
♪ Why, you know I'd rather
hang than have a wife ♪
♪ I know I said
I'd make you mine ♪
♪ now wouldn't youse
know that I would go ♪
♪ for that
old line ♪
♪ how could you
believe me ♪
♪ when I said
I loved you ♪
♪ when you know
I've been a liar ♪
♪ you sure have
been a liar ♪
♪ a double-crossin'
liar ♪
♪ all my doggone
cheatin' life? ♪
♪ You said you would
love me long ♪
So what?
♪ And never would
do me wrong ♪
Stop bending the suit!
♪ Faithful
you'd always be ♪
Me?
♪ Why, baby,
you must be loony ♪
♪ to trust a lower-than-low
two-timer like me ♪
♪ you said I'd
have everything ♪
Get her.
♪ A beautiful
diamond ring ♪
♪ A bungalow
by the sea ♪
A bungalow yet.
♪ You're really naive
to ever believe ♪
♪ a full-of-baloney
phony like me ♪
Boy, I sure must've lost my head.
You ain't lost nothin' you never had.
♪ What about the time
you went to Indiana? ♪
♪ I was lyin' ♪
♪ I was down
in Ala... Bam ♪
♪ you said you
had some business ♪
♪ you had
to complete ♪
♪ what I was doin' ♪
♪ I would be a cad
to repeat ♪
♪ what about the evenin's
you was with your mother? ♪
♪ I was rompin' with
another honey lamb ♪
♪ to think you swore
our love was real ♪
♪ baby, leave us not
forget that I'm a heel ♪
♪ how could I believe you
when you said you loved me? ♪
♪ When you know
I've been a liar ♪
♪ a good-for-nothin'
liar ♪
♪ all my good-for-nothin'
life ♪
♪ You know you've
been a liar ♪
♪ I know I've
♪ a double-crossin'
liar ♪
♪ all your good-for-nothin' life ♪
Johnny!
Darling, I just had to come.
I just had to.
Who's that with Ellen?
Oh, I'm so glad.
The chap with the accent.
Who?
Yes.
Him?
Ah.
Brindale.
They've become very good friends.
Oh, yes.
Don't you think we should
be getting over to Edgar's?
Later, Johnny.
Tonight's my night,
and tonight I want
to be alone with you.
When you didn't show up
at the opening,
I didn't even feel like going on.
How'd you get away from your party?
Oh, I just walked out.
I couldn't stand not
being with you tonight.
Ellen...
Ellen, I think we're in love.
Yes, darling.
I know.
Well, what are we
going to do about it?
Nothing.
Well, we can't go on
in this indefinite state.
Well, aren't you happy?
Oh, you know I am.
So am I.
Let's not kill it
with improvements, huh?
But... something
might happen.
Like what?
Well, someday you might
look over my shoulder
and see someone else.
Someone else?
Yes.
♪ Too late now
to forget your smile ♪
♪ the way we cling when
we've danced a while ♪
♪ too late now to forget
and go on ♪
♪ to someone new ♪
♪ too late now
to forget your voice ♪
♪ the way one word
makes my heart rejoice ♪
♪ too late now
to imagine myself ♪
♪ away from you ♪
♪ all the things
we've done together ♪
♪ I relive
when we're apart ♪
♪ all the tender fun
together ♪
♪ stays on in my heart ♪
♪ how could I ever
close the door ♪
♪ and be the same
as I was before? ♪
♪ Darling, no, no,
I can't anymore ♪
♪ it's too ♪
♪ late ♪
♪ now ♪
Does Tom know how you feel?
Oh, goodness, no.
Do you think he'd mind?
Well, I imagine if he ever found out,
he'd get us a booking someplace in South
Africa just to get me away from you.
Would you forget about
me in South Africa?
But how could I?
♪ All the things
we've done together ♪
♪ I relive
when we're apart ♪
♪ all the tender fun
together ♪
♪ stays on in my heart ♪
♪ how could I ever
close the door ♪
♪ and be the same
as I was before? ♪
♪ Darling, no ♪
♪ no, I can't anymore ♪
♪ it's too late ♪
♪ now ♪
Who is it?
It's me, Jamie. Tom.
Tommy, me boy, come in.
Are you all closed up for the night?
Well, it's after 2:00.
But I'd never close
for you, Tommy boy.
Thanks. The show went well, eh?
Oh, fine, fine.
I didn't feel like going home
straight after the party,
so I thought I'd stop
by and say hello.
Well, you're just in time.
It was announced we go to see
the presents on Monday.
I was just about to try on
me suit for the palace.
I'll slip into it, you have a look,
then you can tell me
what you think, eh?
Sure.
Oh, uh, by the way,
isn't this Anne's night to visit you?
Yeah, she was by about an hour ago,
picked up her money, and
stole away like a pickpocket.
Did her call come
through from Chicago?
No, the bloomin' blighter
never called.
She must be upset.
Well, I couldn't say.
I don't know how Annie
feels about anything.
She's not an easy one to get to know.
Very quiet she is, but deep.
At least I hope she is deep.
Or else she's wasting
a lot of her time being quiet.
Well, brace yourself.
What do you think?
Do I look like a gentleman?
Jamie, you look like a banker.
But do I look like a gentleman?
It's written all over you.
I got it this afternoon
from Percy Monroe.
Last year when he got pneumonia,
they bought it for him
to be buried in.
But he recovered.
Well, my only advice is...
If you meet the royal family...
I wouldn't bow too low.
Remember, this is a wedding,
not a coming-out party.
I see what you mean.
I'll watch it.
Are you excited?
Excited, no.
I'm just scared.
Why?
Nervous and scared.
It's meetin' the old crow again.
I haven't clapped eyes
on her in 3 years.
I know.
It's funny, but if it wasn't
for this royal wedding,
probably I'd never have
crossed her path again.
I'll tell you what: On
Monday I'll call for you,
take you down to meet her.
I'll give you moral support.
Now, that's nice of you, Tommy.
Unusually nice of you.
You're a good man, you are.
I don't know what Annie is doing
waiting for this
knucklehead in Chicago
when she knows a fella like
you right here in town.
That's love, Jamie.
What about you?
Do I look like
the settling-down kind?
Come on. Let me out.
I'll do the bending.
I'm dressed for it.
Thank you, Tommy.
Good night, buddy.
Good night, fella.
♪ Everywhere that beauty
goes you are ♪
♪ everywhere an orchid grows
you are ♪
♪ everything
that's young and gay ♪
♪ brighter than a holiday ♪
♪ everywhere
the angels play ♪
♪ you are ♪
♪ you're like Paris
in April and may ♪
♪ you're New York
on a silvery day ♪
♪ a Swiss alp
as the sun grows fainter ♪
♪ you're Loch Lomond
when Autumn is the painter ♪
♪ you're moonlight
on a night in Capri ♪
♪ and Cape Cod
looking out at the sea ♪
♪ you're all places
that leave me breathless ♪
♪ and no wonder ♪
♪ you're all the world
to me ♪
♪ Every night at 7:00 ♪
Come in!
Oh, morning. Oh, hello, Edgar.
Absolutely fantastic
notices, every one!
You can stay on for years.
Have you seen the dailies?
Rather!
Oh, we're so thrilled.
There's been an 8-week call
at the libraries.
There's been a what at the what?
The libraries, old boy.
That's what we call
our ticket brokers.
They want blocks of seats,
8 weeks in advance.
Why didn't you say so?
Oh, Tom, do you see the one
where they say we're brilliant?
Where?
Oh, Edgar, have you
called Irving yet?
I'm off to the office now.
I'll take it in my room.
Edgar, sit down a second, will ya?
I want you to do a favor for me.
Oh, at your command, old boy.
Look, when you call Irving,
ask him to find out
what happened to a boy
who used to work at Ogilvy's
department store in Chicago.
His name is, uh, Hal Rayton.
I've written it all down.
Oh, right you are.
Will you do that?
And, uh, don't say anything
to anybody about it, will ya?
It shall be graveyard, old boy,
graveyard.
Cheerio. All right. Thanks.
This is New York.
We're ready, London.
Mr. Irving Klinger
is on the line.
Hello, hello!
Irving there?
Edgar here.
Hey, Eddie, so how are things?
Buzzing right along.
A smash, huh?
So how were the notices?
Wizard, old boy, wizard!
That bad, huh?
No, no, no, no.
Wizard.
Wiz-ard!
Oh, wiz...
Yes.
Now, look,
Tom wants you to follow up on a chap
named Hal Rayton.
R-a-y-t-o-n.
Hal Rayton, huh?
What does he do, a single?
No, Mr. Rayton is not in
the theatrical profession.
He ain't in the theater,
so who needs him?
Oh, it's a personal matter of Tom's.
Now, when last heard from,
Mr. Rayton was employed
at Ogilvy's department
store in Chicago.
Ogilvy's. Dig ya.
I'll throw the hassle
to our Chicago branch,
have the whole mess in
your lap in a fast 2 days.
Oh, no, no. That
won't be necessary.
Just follow up on the Rayton
matter and let us know.
Natch. I just said...
pip, now.
Oh, uh, yes, um...
Uh, dig... You!
Oh! There's Jamie
for you.
Wouldn't you know he'd be
late, even to the palace!
Now, take it easy, mother.
Maybe the traffic was heavy.
Oh, it's not the traffic. It's Jamie.
Ever since I told him I don't
like to be kept waiting,
he's been keeping me waiting.
You know, mother,
there's an old Spanish proverb which goes,
"he who does not love the
faults of his loved one
does not love
at all."
Hmm. That may be well
and good for the Spanish,
but I'm English.
You know what I think? No, dearie.
I think he's all excited
about seeing you.
You think so?
How do I look?
As elegant as can be.
Tommy, tell him he's going too fast.
Driver, could you slow down a little?
Yes, sir.
What say we step off
and have a quick one?
To the health
of the royal couple, eh?
Sit back, Jamie. We're
not stopping anywhere.
Well, tell him to go a little slower.
He can't go any slower.
Don't be so nervous.
And when you see her,
be sure and act like the
gentleman you look like.
I will, but if she says
one word of criticism,
I'll hit her on the head
with this cap.
You'll do nothing of the kind.
Here we are.
Stop here, driver.
We'll walk the rest of the way.
Come on now. Don't lose
your nerve. Get in there.
Go on.
Hello, Jamie.
Good day, Sarah.
Jamie, your suit's handsome.
Handsome.
Thank you.
I'm, uh, I'm sorry I'm late.
The traffic was heavy today.
I told the cabby to go
as fast as he could.
Shall we go?
Allow me.
Jamie, don't.
I knew they'd hold.
There are some days when
you can do nothing wrong.
Do you think they'll stay together?
Sure.
I hope so.
For them as well as for me.
I could never have left mother alone.
Now you can get married
and forget about her.
Yes.
Yeah?
Good evening.
Edgar.
I have the information you requested
regarding
Mr. Rayton.
Ohh, what? Well,
it's nothing terribly exciting.
Mr. Rayton still
works at Ogilvy's.
He's still in the luggage department.
He used to live in Chicago proper,
but not long ago he and
his wife moved to Evanston.
His wife?!
Why, yes,
he was married several months ago.
My, my, my.
I say, who is this chap anyway?
Oh, uh, he was engaged
to a girl in the show.
I was just finding out
about him for her.
Oh, I say, that's frightful!
Yes, isn't it?
Well, what are you so pleased about?
I always smile when I'm heartbroken.
I better tell her.
Oh, not now.
Don't you think you should wait
till after the performance?
It would seem kinder.
Maybe you're right.
Edgar, you're a real pal.
I'd stick up for you anytime.
Well, thanks, old chap.
That's frightfully
decent of you to say.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Oh! I shall be around to pick
you up early tomorrow morning.
What's tomorrow?
Why, the royal wedding.
And I shall take you someplace
where you'll see all the pageantry.
Great.
- Second act, Mr. Bowen.
- Right.
♪ I left my hat ♪
♪ in Haiti ♪
♪ in some forgotten flat
in Haiti ♪
♪ I couldn't tell you
how I got there ♪
♪ I only know it was so ♪
♪ hot there ♪
♪ she took my hat ♪
♪ politely ♪
♪ and wound her arms
around me tightly ♪
♪ but I remember
nothing clearly ♪
♪ except the flame
when she came near me ♪
♪ her eyes ♪
♪ had the fire
of surrender ♪
♪ and her touch,
it was tender ♪
♪ and I guess
in a moment as that ♪
♪ you forget
about your hat ♪
♪ so if you go to Haiti ♪
♪ there is a girl I know
in Haiti ♪
♪ if you can find her ♪
♪ you'll adore her ♪
♪ just look around
till you've found ♪
♪ someone who has
a blue-gray fedora ♪
♪ I think of
that gorgeous creature ♪
♪ when I'm all alone ♪
♪ whenever I do,
from down inside there comes ♪
♪ a groan ♪
♪ that son of a gun
in Haiti ♪
♪ has got
the prettiest hat I own ♪
♪ and when
it's bleak and chilly ♪
♪ and life is flat ♪
♪ I think of
that Haitian dilly ♪
♪ and think
I better go get my hat ♪
♪ I left my hat ♪
♪ in Haiti ♪
♪ in some forgotten flat
in Haiti ♪
♪ I couldn't tell you
how I got there ♪
♪ I only know it was so ♪
♪ hot there ♪
♪ But I remember
nothing clearly ♪
♪ except the flame
when she came near me ♪
♪ her eyes ♪
♪ had the fire
of surrender ♪
♪ and her touch,
it was tender ♪
♪ and I guess
in a moment as that ♪
♪ you forget
about your hat ♪
♪ so if you go to Haiti ♪
♪ there is a girl I know
in Haiti ♪
♪ if you can find her,
you'll adore her ♪
♪ just look around
till you've found ♪
♪ someone who has
a blue-gray fedora ♪
Ellen.
Got anybody to take you home?
Good.
Good night,
Mr. Bowen.
Good night.
Anne, I've something to tell you.
Yes.
I hope you won't think I've butted
in where I shouldn't have, but...
Jamie told me
your friend didn't call.
I didn't ask.
He told me.
I don't quite know why I did it,
but I decided to try and find
out what happened to him.
Did you?
Yes, I did.
Well?
Anne.
He's married.
Married?
I'm sorry.
How wonderful.
How simply wonderful.
Oh, Tom, thank you.
Oh, it was nothing.
Anne...
Here I've been worrying myself to
death over him on account of you,
and he's been married all the time.
Isn't it wonderful?
What do you mean, on account of me?
Well, on account of me being in love
with you and you being in love with me.
I'm in love with you?
Well, aren't you?
Yeah.
What a mess.
Why?
The next thing that happens,
we'll be thinking
about getting married.
I'm thinking about it right now.
There. You see?
Well, don't you want to marry me?
Yes, I do.
Anne, it isn't you.
It's marriage.
I'm afraid I couldn't be
married and make a go of it.
I've been living one way too long.
For me, it's always been work.
Everything else has
just been a side issue.
It isn't because I don't want to.
It's just that I...
I don't know if I could change.
Anne...
I know I'd be an awful
flop as a husband.
Do you understand?
I think I do, Tom.
What do we do?
Perhaps you better take me home.
Tom...
I only disagree with one thing.
What's that?
I think you'd make
a marvelous husband.
You do?
Yes, I do, Tom.
Hi.
You're back early.
It isn't early.
I thought it was.
Well, it isn't.
It's late.
Is it?
I didn't say anything.
Tom, John wants to marry me.
He does?
That's funny.
Well, it might be to you,
but it's terribly serious to him.
He's very much in love with me,
and he said he's found
a new faith in everything
all on account of me.
How do you feel?
Well... very constructive.
I never thought
I'd live to see the day
you'd inspire anybody to do
anything but slug it out.
All right, go ahead, make fun of me.
I'm sorry, Ellie.
You really are involved
this time, aren't you?
Up to here.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I was rather hoping
you'd make up my mind for
me like you usually do.
It sure is funny.
Why do you keep saying that
when it isn't funny at all?!
It's very important.
I know it is.
I only meant it's funny because...
Anne wants me to marry her.
She does?
My gosh.
It sure is funny, isn't it?
Why?
Well, I don't know.
It's just funny, that's all.
Now, what's so funny about
someone wanting to marry me?
I have a few good points, you know.
Tommy,
are you really in love with her?
Up to here.
Oh, my.
Well...
I wonder what would happen
if we just threw over
all our principles
and went ahead and
got married anyway.
You'd stay here
in England with John...
why would I stay here?
You can't go traipsing
all over the world
and leave your husband at home.
What kind of a marriage
would that be?
No, I...
I suppose not.
Well...
well, what would you do?
I'd marry Anne...
no, no, I mean who
would you dance with?
Well, I never thought of that.
Not having you,
I might try Anne if she wants to.
She loves to dance and
shows a lot of promise.
Do you really think so?
Yeah.
I thought she was a
little awkward myself.
So were you when you started.
Well, I know it,
but it takes years
to build a good team.
You've always said that.
And there's a lot
of excitement in doing it.
Well, it just isn't fair, Tom.
What isn't?
What? I'm getting the
short end of the stick.
You want me to settle back
and get out of the way
while you go off with someone
else and have all the fun.
I think it's rotten of
you, Tommy, simply rotten.
I didn't ask...
everything's been so perfect.
We've had a wonderful life together.
We've been very successful.
How can you even
consider breaking it up?
And breaking it up for what?
To get married.
Oh, no, Tom.
Marriage is a tough business.
You know, I've always thought marr...
responsibilities, obligations,
a home to take care of.
Maybe children to look after.
Imagine being married to
someone you're dancing with.
If either the marriage or
the dancing doesn't work out,
both of them go kaplooey!
Oh, no. No, Thomas.
It's a terrible chance to take.
It is, isn't it?
We mustn't do it.
We've slaved too hard to get where we are.
Why should we give it up?
It does seem foolish, doesn't it?
We're a team, and a darn good one.
We ought to stay that way.
Maybe you're right.
Well, of course I'm right.
Oh, you do see it, don't you, Tommy?
Sure I see it.
It's you and me,
just like it's always been.
I'm sure we're doing the right thing.
Thank you so much
for deciding for me.
Forget it.
♪ What a lovely day
for a wedding ♪
♪ happy are we to say ♪
♪ it's a lovely day
for a wedding ♪
♪ lovely in every way ♪
♪ there's families out,
without a doubt ♪
♪ to see what
all the joy's about ♪
♪ for everywhere the world
is merry and gay ♪
♪ what a lovely day
for a wedding ♪
♪ over again we say ♪
♪ it's a lovely, lovely,
lovely wedding day ♪
♪ what a lovely day
for a wedding ♪
♪ happy are we
to say ♪
♪ what a lovely day
for a wedding ♪
♪ lovely in every way ♪
♪ the royal guard
is off their guard ♪
♪ and drink is got
at Scotland yard ♪
♪ big Ben has quite
forgot the time of the day ♪
♪ what a lovely day
for a wedding ♪
♪ over again we say ♪
♪ it's a lovely,
lovely wedding ♪
♪ a lovely, lovely
wedding ♪
♪ lovely ♪
♪ wedding day ♪
Hello.
Good morning, old chappy!
Hello, Edgar.
Good morning. I've come
to take you to the wedding.
And what a wedding parade
we shall see.
Are you ready?
As ready as I'll ever be.
I say, what's the matter
with you two this morning?
You're all at sixes and sevens.
Nothing's the matter. Let's go.
Tom, I want...
Ellie, I've got to
have her. I lose.
So what? I want to
get married today.
Today? Sure, before I change my mind.
Think we can do it?
We must do it. Edgar,
we want to get married.
I thought you two were related.
No, no. And we want
to get married today.
Why, it takes 3 weeks.
3 weeks? Anything
can happen in 3 weeks.
Irving says you can do anything.
You can fix it for us.
I know, but one must have permission
from the archbishop's office,
and after all, he's busy today.
You've got to swing it for us, Edgar.
Well, I'll try.
You two meet me
at the vicar general's in 2 hours,
and if it's at all possible to
get permission for a license,
where? You shall be
married this afternoon.
Clyde street church.
I believe I know the minister there.
This is a pretty box of pickles.
I beg your pardon, sir.
Now we...
now we have to find Anne and John.
In these crowds?
I know what corner she's standing on.
Where's John?
He should be leaving the Abbey
for the reception any minute now.
Well, you better find him.
Ellie, I'm gonna miss you
a lot from now on.
Oh, Tommy, you're
a wonderful brother.
Good luck, darling.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Will you excuse me?
John!
Ellen!
What's the matter?!
John, I wanna marry you!
What?!
I said I want to marry you!
You do?!
Yes!
Clyde street church
at 4:00!
Right!
Here, here! What do you
think you're doing?
Oh, officer, I love you!
Anne!
Tom!
Will ya marry me?!
What?!
Yes!
Good-bye.
They didn't have to go
to all this trouble.
A small wedding
would've been all right.